Guide to the Mary Dowdell Ashley Film Collection, 1937-1975 RL.10048
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Films, 1936-1967; 1
  - Reel 2, compilation, segments 13-24, 1956-1958; 2
    Reel 2. Sequence 16. Scene 4. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Shap & Myrick dressed for Sunday School; Ginny in white coat, Bonnie & Ann with Shap, Mollie & Myrick.
    Reel 2. Sequence 16. Scene 5. Bankhead Avenue, backyard: sliding board & swing set. Mother in dark jacket & bermuda shorts & others; then close-up of Mother.
    Reel 2. Sequence 16. Scene 6. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Uncle Eddie, Little Ann, Mother & Daddy. DARK.
    Reel 2. Sequence 16. Scene 7. Coosa: Daddy cooking; Bonnie ?; 2 boys at creek: may be Myrick on right & Randolph Candler on left; foreground: Shap; shots of foliage & then "falls"; Myrick & Randolph Candler at bottom of the "falls."
    Reel 2. Sequence 17. Scene. Family trip to Jamestown & Williamsburg for 350th anniversary of landing at Jamestown. On the return trip, the family went to Ocracoke Island off the coast of North Carolina.
    Reel 2. Sequence 17. Scene 1. Virginia Department of Highways car ferry: Myrick - Shap - Daddy - Ann, then Ginny on far left & Bonnie on far right.
    Reel 2. Sequence 17. Scene 2. Jamestown: Shap & Bonnie; stocks, then Bonnie standing & Shap in stocks; 3 ship replicas (the Susan Constant, the Godspeed, and the Discovery): Myrick in white short-sleeved shirt; miscellaneous???; Daddy (large checkered blue & white shirt), then Mother in colored sleeveless dress with boat in background; back of Daddy walking away from camera; Myrick (barefooted), Shap & Bonnie.
    Reel 2. Sequence 17. Scene 3. On boat (CHECK ON WHICH BOAT): Bonnie's back & Ann on right, Myrick on left and Bonnie on right; Daddy at back with Myrick's head in Daddy's lap; Shap sticking out tongue; Ginny & Ann next to Daddy & Bonnie sitting in bottom of boat; Bonnie on back.
    Reel 2. Sequence 18. Scene. Family trip continued to Ocracoke after Jamestown.
    Reel 2. Sequence 18. Scene 1. Ocracoke, NC: Bonnie, Shap, Daddy walking; inlet scene; Shap in foreground -- other family members plus some in background; large anchor with Shap on left & Myrick on right; more inlet scenes; house, which might be one our family rented; store ?.
    Reel 2. Sequence 18. Scene 2. Trip to Bird Island: Guide took family there in a small boat: Ginny in foreground; behind, Shap & pelicans - young with mother; pelican eggs in nest; bird guide feeding a pelican; Ginny at back with Myrick & Ann; pelicans; naked newborn pelican in nest; bird guide holding young herons; ? bird species; view of shoreline of Ocracoke or another island.
    Reel 2. Sequence 18. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue, side yard: Marshall & Exie in front of banana plant.
    Reel 2. Sequence 19. Scene 1. Perdido: scenes with boats & people in water & on boat.. Close-up of perhaps a member of the Garth family & Daddy; girls with life waist supports - think Ann is on left.
    Reel 2. Sequence 19. Scene 2. Lake Martin, AL?: on shore and then water; man in hat & Ann Ely in straw hat; more people; Ann Ely & perhaps her husband, Clauson.
    Reel 2. Sequence 19. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Myrick; Ann in striped shirt & friend in red; Shap at front door where Ann joins him.
    Reel 2. Sequence 20. Scene 1. Von Gal's swimming pool: several people; Daddy in water; Ann on diving board from which she does a flip; Daddy in pool with Shap in large inner tube; Suzie von Gal holding fondu dish & walking in front of banana plant beside pool; Shap in inner tube in pool; June von Gal in yellow (white trunks); pool: Daddy holding Shap & Uncle Eddie holding Mollie; Shap & Mollie swimming; Marney von Gal in raft with a child; Shap swims; pool scenes with many people.
    Reel 2. Sequence 20. Scene 2. Perdido, AL: ? is skiing; beach: Rusty Seawell in multi-colored straw hat; Ginny ? in black suit skiing; Margaret Harris in strapless yellow bathing suit with Shap behind her, then Myrick on left; more water & skiing; Ann doing a flip off diving board; canoe with Ginny at front - Margaret Harris may be at back - Myrick is in the water.
    Reel 2. Sequence 21. Scene 1. Coosa, AL: probably birthday party for Myrick & Shap: creek at base of falls; close-up of crawfish; woods: Daddy & Shap in striped shirt; friends of Myrick & Shap, toasting marshmellows; close-up of snagle-toothed Myrick; friends; Randolph Candler ? with marshmellow on foot' friends in woods. Jack's Creek: sandy beach on other side of creek; scenes of friends & old mill site.
    Reel 2. Sequence 21. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, front porch: Julian Hart, Shap holding red hat, & Billy Joseph; dressed for Sunday School: Ginny in red suit behind Myrick, Bonnie, Billy Joseph & younger brother ? & Ann
    Reel 2. Sequence 22. Scene 1. Mary Esther, FL,Deep Sea Fishing in Gulf: Ann fishing from back of boat; Ginny with Shap in lap, holding pole; Bonnie in pony tails & Shap; Daddy holding fishing pole; Myrick eating; Ann catching fish again; Bonnie despondent; Ann, Daddy, & Ginny on other side of Daddy; Jane Marks fishing. After fishing trip on pier on Sound: Shap, Ginny, Jane Marks, Ann, Bonnie - each holding a fish; close-ups, then Daddy beside Shap; ? & Exie on pier; Shap holding fish; Myrick holding crab net; Shap swimming.
    Reel 2. Sequence 22. Scene 2. Montgomery, AL: Swim meet at the "Y" ?
    Reel 2. Sequence 22. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Myrick OR SHAP? 2 friends on right -- all in football attire; playing football in yard.
    Reel 2. Sequence 22. Scene 4. Montgomery, AL: Murchison's front yard: hula hoop contest -- Ann using hula hoop; DARK, but may be Bonnie in plaid; Shap using hula hoop; small female using hula hoop; back to Ann & hula hoop.
    Reel 2. Sequence 23. Scene 1. Montgomery, AL: Floyd School playground: football game & cheerleaders.
    Reel 2. Sequence 23. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Betty Seale, Ginny, Bonnie, Debbie Moorer, Myrick, all holding Tootsie's puppies; Myrick on bike; Debbie Moorer & Bonnie with puppies & Tootsie on ground.
    Reel 2. Sequence 23. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue, back yard: volleyball game -- Bonnie in pony tails; Exie on 2nd floor back porch; Ann & Rosalind Weil on other side of fence in dresses.
    Reel 2. Sequence 23. Scene 4. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Shap, Myrick, Julian Hart, & Joe Thetford, each holding a puppy.
    Reel 2. Sequence 23. Scene 5. Coosa, AL: front of house? Gray Thames? Ann -- more of Ann &/or Bonnie's friends. Jack's Creek: on rock facing camera -- Debbie Moorer; Gray Thames & Bonnie in water; scenes of friends, etc. on rocks & in water.
    Reel 2. Sequence 24. Scene 1. Montgomery Country Club: Blue-Gray Tennis Tournament; DARK; Ann as ball girl.
    Reel 2. Sequence 24. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue; Myrick in cowboy hat carrying full laundry bag.
    Reel 2. Sequence 24. Scene 3. Montgomery, AL: Von Gal's swimming pool: group of kids, but DARK.
    Reel 2. Sequence 24. Scene 4. Montgomery, AL: "Y" or Maxwell Air Force Base swimming pool: swim meet.
    Reel 2. Sequence 24. Scene 5. Mary Esther, FL: ? Skiing; Daddy on boat & behind him, Myrick & Ann & Shap & Ginny.
    Reel 2. Sequence 24. Scene 6. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Exie in front of house (good picture of house).
    - Original 16mm film, 1956-1958; 1300 film feet (Box 1, Film-reel RL10048-F16-0002)
  - Reel 3, compilation, segments 25-36, circa 1960; 3
    Original notes on can:
    Montgomery, AL; Coosa County, AL; Mentone, AL; Perdido, AL; New England; New York; Farmington, CT; Lynchburg, VA; Destin, FL; Mexico City; Acapulco, Mexico
    Reel 3. Sequence 25. Scene 1. Bankhead Avenue, front & side yards: Tootsie & her puppies; Shap in gray blazer, Ann in red coat, Ginny in white coat, Bonnie in lavender/purple dress, Myrick (snaggletoothed) in light blue blazer; Daddy with big box & Myrick inside. Myrick & Little Allen? (beige pants).
    Reel 3. Sequence 25. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, vacant lot across street: group playing ball; view of our house.
    Reel 3. Sequence 25. Scene 3. Montgomery, AL: Von Gal's yard: adults & children; Myrick & Little Ann; close-up of Suzy von Gal; June von Gal with cigarette in mouth; Ann in blue dress; Edith Johnston on right of screen; Marney von Gal in red, black, gray striped skirt; Ginny in corduroy jumper; view of our house; ? in red t shirt, lying on ground; Shap with basketball; Daddy in brown hat next to June von Gal; Bonnie in red, blue, white plaid shirt with back to camera; Shap playing with a football; Bonnie with Ann on her back; Marney von Gal & Ginny; Bonnie with Edith Johnston on her back; close up of Edith Johnston (Mrs. Watt Johnston).
    Reel 3. Sequence 25. Scene 4. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Shap, Bonnie, Edith Johnston, Ann, Myrick.
    Reel 3. Sequence 26. Scene 1. Montgomery, AL: downtown: Lanier Homecoming Parade.
    Reel 3. Sequence 26. Scene 2. Montgomery, AL, Coliseum: horse show: presentation of awards -- Bonnie in green dress & Carey Murchison in white dress; Mrs. Murchison in brown striped top.
    Reel 3. Sequence 26. Scene 3. Coosa, AL: front of house: Thanksgiving Day: Aunt Jeanette, Ada, Big Ann, back of Little Ann in red plaid pants, holding Ann D, Aunt Annie in blue; close-up of Ada; Mollie holding Big Ann's hand, Aunt Minnie in blue to right; backs of station wagons with Daddy nearest cars; Myrick in white top, Bonnie with Uncle Eddie (dark glasses) behind her & then Ginny.
    Reel 3. Sequence 26. Scene 3. Coosa,AL cont'd: view of house; group walking down path, perhaps toward the "spout;" backs of station wagons with ball, pillows, thermos, drink jug, coolers; group playing to right of backs of station wagons & in front of large dark car; Shap in white top holding sticks; close-up of Uncle Crawf (hat & horn-rimmed glasses); Uncle Eddie; close-up of Daddy; Mollie & Shap at back of station wagons.
    Reel 3. Sequence 26. Scene 4. Montgomery, AL: Floyd School: Mrs. Haber's class of Shap & his classmates: Shap in costume (purple cape); several of his classmates; Julian Hart (red shorts) dancing with ?.
    Reel 3. Sequence 26. Scene 5. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Myrick, Bonnie, Shap playing ball; Shap & Myrick with football; Bonnie in pastel dress.
    Reel 3. Sequence 27. Scene 1. Montgomery, AL: "Y" swim meet: Shap may be in red trunks; Ann may be doing the butterfly.
    Reel 3. Sequence 27. Scene 2. Montgomery Country Club, tennis courts: ball girls behind adult female ? Betty Carr?; at top of ball girls is Ann & on right is Bonnie with pony tail & headband; table with awards with Kitty or Peggy Shertzer seated on closest side of table; Barry Harmon may be behind Ann at top.
    Reel 3. Sequence 27. Scene 3. Mentone, AL: Camp Skyline: waterfront: synchronized swimming with Ginny possibly one of swimmers; 2 in white on pier; Sydney Smith on left & Ann may be on right; others (?) appear. DARK. Bonnie walking towards camera; cakewalk on tennis courts - little dark; Shap (orange & black striped t shirt) drinking from cup; DARK, but Ginny ? on left & Ann ? on right.
    Reel 3. Sequence 28. Scene 1. Mentone, AL: Camp Skyline: waterfront: audience view; swimmers in water -- possibly playing water hockey; DARK; close-up of Ann in black swimsuit; canoe contest; small motorboat; large group in water.
    Reel 3. Sequence 28. Scene 2. Mentone, AL: Camp Laney: Myrick in blue & white striped shirt; Daddy in plaid Bermuda shorts.
    Reel 3. Sequence 28. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Bonnie - Ginny- Ann; Bonnie swinging Ginsie & then an older girl; Big Ann holding straw bag on porch; Ann D. ? playing football: Randolph Candler in black on left; Shap in blue/black/white striped t shirt & Myrick in red/yellow/black striped t shirt; tall boy with the 3 is Gene Thetford; Shap in contortionish position.
    Reel 3. Sequence 28. Scene 4. Bankhead Avenue, back yard: concrete slab: 2 boys on right, Myrick with back to camera & Shap. Ann ? In red vest sitting on stool or table; Bonnie in red plaid pants sitting; Mollie & Ann D.; angle shot with banana tree on left; Daddy seated at table & Myrick in foreground; Bonnie on back with Mollie standing or sitting on her feet (upstretched legs).
    Reel 3. Sequence 29. Scene 1. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: All dressed for Sunday School &/or church: close-up of Shap, then Ann, then Myrick, then Bonnie, then Shap; Bonnie & Mother in white hat - Ann, Shap, & Myrick standing in front of Mother; then Shap, Ann, Daddy, Bonnie, Myrick.
    Reel 3. Sequence 29. Scene 2. Perdido, AL: launching of Judge Thetford's boat; DARK, but group with Daddy in middle after boat launching; close-up of Judge Thetford driving boat with someone? skiing. DARK: cliffs beside water.
    Reel 3. Sequence 29. Scene 3. Montgomery Country club: tennis courts: several playing tennis; ball boys & girls but hard to distinguish who they are.
    Reel 3. Sequence 29. Scene 4. Bankhead Avenue? ? In green top & pants on left; Ann in navy shorts; back of ?
    Reel 3. Sequence 29. Scene 5. Bankhead Avenue, driveway: Bonnie on left and Susan Selman ? on right beside white & blue Plymouth station wagon; front of rearview of green Plymouth; Shap in red wild hat or fake hair.
    Reel 3. Sequence 29. Scene 6. Perdido, AL: Joe? Thetford & Shap & older boy & little girl? in water; several children splashing.
    Reel 3. Sequence 30. Scene 1. Perdido, AL: Small boat with motor: on left boys? & back of ? In striped shirt & orange life jacket covering his top; girl? on left; sailboat next to other boat; ? with dark hair at front with 2 girls behind her. Motor boat pulls sailboat. Briefly at Gulf near Perdido: fairly dark interior of boat. Back at Perdido: close-up of Daddy in white shirt holding a fish, Withers Davis, Sr. in dark glasses; close-up of Alice Davis in sleeveless white shirt; close-up of Raymond Boykin in straw hat.
    Reel 3. Sequence 30. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue: Phoebe's kittens & Myrick in blue striped t shirt holding a kitten; DARK: kittens & close-up of Phoebe.
    Reel 3. Sequence 30. Scene 3. Montgomery, AL: Von Gal's swimming pool: June von Gal in red plaid trunks by fire; pool scene: Bonnie? on raft; close-up of Myrick; Shap lying on raft; Bonnie sitting in raft chair. DARK. Mother holding white object in front of her; close-up of Daddy.
    Reel 3. Sequence 31. Scene 1. Mother's trip to New England to attend the 25th reunion of her class at Miss Porter's School in Farmington, CT. New England coast: views from boat; clam digging by adult male, then adult female in background; young boy carrying bucket; scene of pier & boats; adult male in plaid shirt; view of beach & water; adult female on beach; boy in red jacket. Mother's notes indicate "lobsters," but DARK.
    Reel 3. Sequence 32. Scene 1. Mother's trip to New England (cont'd): Farmington, CT: friends & classmates of Mother at Miss Porter's School; scenes of town; scenes of people; field hockey with current students.
    Reel 3. Sequence 32. Scene 2. Lynchburg, VA: Randolph-Macon Woman's College (RMWC): On her return trip from New England, Mother visited Ginny in her sophomore year at college. Views of campus buildings.
    Reel 3. Sequence 33. Scene 1. Montgomery, AL: Cloverdale School where football game between Cloverdale & Floyd Schools took place: Floyd cheerleaders, including Ann; scene of game; view of Cloverdale (red bMyrick); Ann is closest to camera in scene where can see large "2" on school.
    Reel 3. Sequence 33. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: close-up of Little Ann holding Edward as a baby; Ginsie on ground with red plastic bag; then Ann D. in short-sleeved yellow shirt; Mollie standing to side & in front of magnolia tree; close-up of Shap (blue & brown striped shirt) & Mollie holding "July."
    Reel 3. Sequence 33. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue, back yard: "July" with Phoebe's kittens; laundry basket at back is bed for the kittens; Phoes is large tabby - near screen door of back porch. DARK. Concrete slab in back yard: Myrick in red shirt & friend - Mark Johnson? playing ball. In background: Bonnie in blue & Gray Thames in dark pink.
    Reel 3. Sequence 34. Scene 1. Destin, FL: AEA vacation: close-up of Shap & then Shap fishing; close-up of Daddy wearing hat & red/white/blue plaid shirt. CLARITY NOT GOOD. Bonnie on left & female?; male in striped shirt with back to camera; Mother in blue sweatshirt & white sailor cap; male in red jacket & female - maybe ? & Frances Lamb.
    Reel 3. Sequence 34. Scene 2. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Bonnie in huge flower hat; DARK, & then Bonnie without hat; Shap in navy suit (short pants) holding flowers; Ann in turquoise outfit; Myrick to side on bike; Mother in flowered dress holding kitten; Myrick riding bike.
    Reel 3. Sequence 34. Scene 3. Location? Lake ?: various people skiing; Myrick on pink raft; more skiing; boat; tree; Tullis ____(dark glasses) sitting next to Daddy; people in water; more skiing; Myrick in red plaid trunks on foldable rectangular lounge frame at end of pier; people in water.
    Reel 3. Sequence 34. Scene 4. Bankhead Avenue, front of house: see front door; Shap holding present & standing next to Bonnie.
    Reel 3. Sequence 35. Scene 1. Family trip to Mexico: whole family at ancient ruin (pyramid); close-up of surface of ruin; landscape views; roadside views as driving in car; University playground?; huge concrete slab; Olympic swimming pool with extensions; University buildings; murals on buildings, some close-up.
    Reel 3. Sequence 36. Scene 2. Family trip to Mexico (cont'd): Mexico City bull ring: ceremonial beginning; bullfight - lot is DARK. Driving with landscape views from car.
    Reel 3. Sequence 36. Scene 3. Family trip to Mexico (cont'd): Acapulco: Myrick & Shap at edge of water; view of hotel built into rocks beside water; Bonnie (back to camera) in water; views of water & area near hotel.
    Reel 3. Sequence 36. Scene 4. Family trip to Mexico (cont'd): Highway: our car got stuck, causing traffic to stop & back up; people out of cars; scene with backs of Ginny (short dark hair; in blue skirt & blouse) & Ann (orangish top & light colored skirt); 2 Mexican males in front of them; white & pale blue station wagon (car family traveling in ).
    - Original 16mm film, 1959-1962; 1300 film feet (Box 1, Film-reel RL10048-F16-0003)
  - Reel 4, compilation, segments 37-48, 1962-1965; 4
    37: Mexico 1962 - Taxco. Floyd cheerleading - Bonnie, Gray, Marcia Jackson, Julie; 38: Fall 1962 - Football - Ginnie - Big Ann - Beach; 39: Bankhead - Ann, Edith, Priscilla Crommelin - Bloyd track meet. Gulf - Blue and Gray Tennis. Puppies. Von Gal pool; 40: Sept. 1963 - "Black Top" - Harmons, Davises, Wallers - Lanier parade - Floyd, Bonnie cheerleading. Shap's birthday ('64); 41: Spring 1964 - Floyd baseball - Randolph Macon, Ginny - Swim class, Neill; 42: Summer 1964 - July - Romar Beach - Stausses - Nan Holley - Backyard w/Bonnie's friends. Perdido - Mark Wilson, G. Harris; 43: Fall 1964 - Lanier Homecoming Parade - Bonnie and Marcia Jackson. Coosa picking turnips - Bankhead cookout; 44: Spring 1965 - Coosa w/Rick, Mark and Bart Wilson. Jack's Creek w/Stausses and Big Ann. Gulf; 45: Gulf - Collecting sea oats. Coosa - Gulf - Gray T. Shap, Phillip and Eddie. Falls. Judge Thetford cooking; 46: Destin - Bankhead - Tennis - Ann - Horses - Shap and Friends; 47: Destin - Rick, John C. Trammel and Shap. Frontyard, Dressed Up; 48: Destin w/Stauss Family. Horses on Bankhead - Bonnie on Jabe - Frontyard football.
    Reel 4. Sequence 37. Scene 1. Family trip to Mexico (cont'd): Taxco: buildings; street scenes; driving in car: views.
    Reel 4. Sequence 37. Scene 2. Floyd cheerleaders: Gray Thames closest to camera; one person between her and Bonnie; close-up of some of audience: Rosalind Weil (?) in navy skirt & maybe Ann next to her in white background dress with flowers or fruit; cheerleaders again: Bonnie second closest to camera; football being played; close-up of Edith Johnston (?), next to person in red & white.
    Reel 4. Sequence 37. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue, vacant lot opposite 3516 Bankhead: Bonnie (red hair) on right; Marcia Jackson (?) with Gray Thames (blond hair) behind her.
    Reel 4. Sequence 37. Scene 4. Bankhead Avenue, front yard: Daddy (good shots) at front door; July with him; then Mother holding July, who must be pregnant.
    Reel 4. Sequence 38. Scene 1. Floyd School sign; cheerleaders with school in background: Bonnie closest to camera & Gray Thames closest to black dog; cheerleaders leading football team out; football game in action; cheerleaders; DARK.
    Reel 4. Sequence 38. Scene 2. Hull Street, front yard: Ann D. Stauss on Bonnie's shoulder; Myrick on left in red shirt; Mollie on right; Bonnie swinging Mollie; Bonnie holding Ginsie in red shirt; trunk of car open & ? leaning into it; back of Big Ann (gray suit) & Ann on right; Mollie or Ann D. & then Ann coming towards Big Ann; Little Ann in trench coat & Uncle Eddie in background; Myrick in blue plaid shirt & then with Uncle Eddie; Eddie with Little Ann in trench coat & Mollie or Ann D.; then Big Ann next to Little Ann; Ginsie (?) in red knit hat; Ann looking at Uncle Eddie & Ann D. (?).
    Reel 4. Sequence 38. Scene 3. Destin, FL: On beach, Daddy in chair; Bonnie on stomach & Gray Thames on back on sand; Myrick on back on sand; Shap with straw hat at edge of water; Shap beating ? with stick; shallow water (Gulf) & sea animal (?); Shap -- Bonnie -- Gray -- Myrick; close-up of Bonnie in straw hat; close-ups of Gray Thames, Myrick, Shap; views of sand.
    Reel 4. Sequence 38. Scene 4. ? & Myrick & Joe Thetford (?).
    Reel 4. Sequence 39. Scene 1. Bankhead Avenue: Ann in white leaning on fence talking to? in plaid shorts with Bonnie to right holding onto ?; ? in plaid shorts standing by herself.
    Reel 4. Sequence 39. Scene 2. Montgomery, AL: Floyd School: track meet: ???? viewing track meet; Ann leaning on fence and others (?); close-up of blonde (?) next to Ann in long-sleeved white shirt; Debbie Moorer & Gray Thames with mouth open & ?; close-up of Debbie next to Gray (faces only); Gray next to Daddy coming towards camera; then see Debbie behind Gray; maybe Debbie running & long jump.
    Reel 4. Sequence 39. Scene 3. Bankhead Avenue: Edith Johnston holding puppy; Ann's head; head down (white with red trim dress; then Priscilla Crommelin holding puppy & Ann (orange shorts); then Edith Johnston in white blouse looking down; Priscilla (in yellow) holding 2 puppies & Edith holding 2 puppies next to ? in white dress with red trim holding puppy; then Priscilla holding 2 puppies; ? in green blouse holding puppy; group scene holding puppies.
    Reel 4. Sequence 39. Scene 4. Location ?: ? In Gulf, then 4 boys; ? -- Myrick -- Mike Harmon; Mike putting on t shirt; Myrick in plaid trunks.
    Reel 4. Sequence 39. Scene 5. Montgomery Country Club: Blue Gray Tennis Tournament, but can't distinguish people.
    Reel 4. Sequence 39. Scene 6. Bankhead Avenue: July's puppies; then with people; Bonnie (?) in blue shorts.
    Reel 4. Sequence 39. Scene 7. Von Gal's swimming pool: Bonnie on raft; Ann with hands against each other; Myrick by side of pool; ? in pool; Suzy von Gal in white walking beside pool; Daddy in red socks walking beside pool; people in water: Myrick holding blue raft; Pat Thetford (?) getting out of pool & Ann (?) in water; Bonnie leaning on blue raft; Annin bathing suit with black design & white on bottom walking on side of pool.
    Reel 4. Sequence 40. Scene 1. Destin, FL (?): Chris Craft boat; piers & boats; on boat: Withers Davis & Barry Harmon, Sr., each in dark glasses; Daddy, smoking, next to ? & Betty Harmon, & then Alice Davis talking to Withers; close-up of ? In white sleeveless shirt with Betty Harmon on her right & ? (male); back of Daddy who is walking along side of boat & ? in blue shirt & Barry Harmon coming towards camera.